SYEDA ANUM FATIMA

REACT NATIVE | REACT.JS | GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ABOUT MYSELF

I am a talented, ambitious, and hardworking individual, with skills in developing websites using React. Js and mobile apps with React Native. I also have vast experience in graphic design. Furthermore, I am adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis competently and at working well under pressure

CONTACT

- Karachi, Pakistan
- anum.syeda110@gmail.com
- +923003505281
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ syeda-anum-fatima-/

EDUCATION

NED UNIVERSITY OF ENGINEERING & TECHNOLOGY

(3.53) ,BE Software Engineering **2018-Present**

METROPOLIS INTERMEDIATE COLLEGE FOR GIRLS,

(85%) Pre-engineering **2016-2018**

CERTIFICATIONS

- Frontend web development (UIT,2018)
- Amal Academy Graduation

(March-June, 2021)

-National Finance Literacy Program **(Sep 2021)**

ADDITIONAL

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS,
 JavaScript,C, C++, C#, React.Js, React
 Native
- Languages: English, Urdu, HSK-I & II

WORK EXPERIENCE

CORPSOLS

DEC 2020 - JAN 2021

Computer Software Company which provides solutions related to web development and mobile application development & other tech services

- Completed a month intern program for developing and designing a WordPress website
- Polished my skills such as HTML, CSS, WordPress elementor while building that project

VOCABULARY BUILDER

MAY 2019- JULY 2019

Windows application using C# programming language on Microsoft Visual Studios which was built to enhance the English vocabulary on basic level and comprised of word and picture quiz along with word jar for daily learning.

NEDIANS' FORUM

JUNE 2020 - SEP 2020

Q&A site as semester project for Web Engineering Course as a Frontend Web Developer

- The project was built for the students of NEDUET to get facilitated through QnA by university alumni, staff and current students
- The project was built using React.js and AWS Lambda functions in the backend. It has similar functions as Stack overflow

BRANDING POTIONS & ADAMS

FEB 2019 - MARCH 2020

Web & Graphic Designer: Designed and managed websites for Branding Potions for 1 year and designed various ads for Adam's garments brand

EXTRACURRICULAR & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS COMMUNITY KARACHI

APRIL 2019 - PRESENT

Team Member Graphics: Was responsible to design & manage social media posts for wordcamps which involve 1.6k learners and conduct various online and onsite sessions to provide learning and information related to WordPress